CHRISTOPHER ANGALET

Portland, OR 97209 | cangalet@gmail.com | 913-269-9273 www.linkedin.com/in/christopher-angalet

SUMMARY

Driven sales and marketing operations professional with 5 years sales support, business operations, reporting and data analysis experience. Exceptional project management skills with the ability to inspire confidence and gain trust through attentive service and efficient resolution of concerns.

AREAS OF EXPERTISE

Salesforce, Jira, MS Office, HTML & CSS, NetSuite, Power BI, Adobe CC, Marketing Automation

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

American City Business Journal, Portland, Oregon

Advertising Specialist

June 2021 – Current

- Entered print, digital and event orders ensuring accurate pricing, breakouts, and products
- Ensured advertising campaigns meet quality assurance by troubleshooting Salesforce and AdBook+ order issues
- Created various reports to assist managers with business objectives
- Maintained data quality by identifying and merging duplicate records, cleansing, and updating inaccurate data
- Provided support for the day-to-day operations of Salesforce by end users

Portland Business Journal, Portland, Oregon

May 2019 – June 2021

Advertising & Business Operations Coordinator

- Trained and educated sales organization about marketing automation capabilities and Salesforce functionality
- Coordinated marketing activities and policies to promote products and services
- Managed all billing with the client and internal accounting processes
- Maintained SharePoint site, ensuring sales organization has up-to-date information on product portfolio
- Developed processes for ad sales and production to receive creative within specifications and on time for print
- Recovered \$250,000 in missing ad revenue between two markets by auditing Power BI and Salesforce system data

Chris Angalet Design, Portland, Oregon

November 2016 - May 2019

Independent Graphic Designer and Marketing Consultant

- Updated copy on sales and marketing collateral to maximize exposure in national markets and increase client base
- Developed, designed, and launched brand identity (e.g. logo, website) and marketing strategy for law firm startup
- Worked with client to rebrand and redesign website to increase web traffic and enhance customer experience

Cerner Corporation, Kansas City, Missouri

March 2017 - September 2017

Support Analyst

- Delivered comprehensive solutions to end-users by utilizing and troubleshooting with tools such as Cerner Millennium Solutions, XenApp, Command Prompt, and GoToAssist
- Provided remote troubleshooting solutions for computer and OS issues affecting software function for over 300 clients
- Applied and contributed to knowledge base of information to quickly identify and diagnose issues

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Business Administration, Cum Laude: Marketing Emphasis

Kansas City, Missouri

Class of 2015

University of Missouri Kansas City

CERTIFICATIONS

Salesforce Admin Certified